dealofthedayindia.com 2015-12-02

# Deal of the day India | Privacy Policy | DealofthedayIndia.com

##  Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

### [Vivo Y51 Launched in China](http://dealofthedayindia.com/blog/?p=2347)

Wednesday, 02 December 2015

Today, Vivo has formally proclaimed a new mid-range smartphone referred to as...

* * *

### [Huawei Enjoy 5s Launch on 3 Dec](http://dealofthedayindia.com/blog/?p=2343)

Wednesday, 02 December 2015

Huawei enjoy 5 that came with a large 4,000mAh battery. The device is priced at...

* * *

### [Phicomm Clue 630 Listed for Online Store](http://dealofthedayindia.com/blog/?p=2333)

Wednesday, 02 December 2015

Phicomm is that the Chinese smartphone manufacturer that had debuted the Indian...

* * *

### [MI4 will get Windows 10 update on 3 Dec](http://dealofthedayindia.com/blog/?p=2328)

Wednesday, 02 December 2015

Today, company’s Founder and President, Lin Bin had announce a picture on...

* * *

### [LG Zero Launched in Europe, Asia & America](http://dealofthedayindia.com/blog/?p=2322)

Wednesday, 02 December 2015

The South Korean big LG has launched a brand new mid-range smartphone dubbed as...

* * *
